vi-view.com 2015-05-09

# Privacy Policy

### TRUSTe's Trusted Download ProgramNew!

Vi-View is certified as a Trusted Download Program by TRUSTe signifying that the Vi-View application has been tested by TRUSTe for compliance with TRUSTe's TDP program requirements including transparency, accountability and choice regarding the collection and use of your personal information. TRUSTe's mission, is to accelerate online trust among consumers and organizations globally through its leading privacy trustmark and innovative trust solutions. If you have questions or complaints regarding the Vi-View application, please contact us at [Flyingbird Technology Limited,FLAT/RM 110，KING‘S COMMERCIAL BUILDING，2-4 CHATHAM COURT，TSIM SHA TSUI，KL，Hong Kong.] or by email at [admin@vi-view.com] or by phone at [+852-27935511]. If you are not satisfied with our response you can contact TRUSTe **[here](http://clicktoverify.truste.com/pvr.php?page=validate&softwareProgramId=535&sealid=112)**.The TRUSTe Trusted Download program covers only Vi-View when downloaded from <http://vi-view.com/> and does not cover other applications such as Search App by Vi-View as a stand-alone application.

As the fastest image viewer in the world, vi-view will be automatically set as your default image viewer. By selecting "Set mystart.vi-view.com as your homepage" checkbox on Vi-view installer primary notice, "Search App by Vi-View" extension will be installed to your Chrome. 

We are committed to protecting your privacy and the security of information you provide to us. Flyingbird Technology Limited ("Flyingbird") will not sell, rent, lease or disclose customer information to third parties unless required by law or unless you provide consent to such a disclosure. Other terms of Flyingbird's privacy policy are as follows: 

### Information Collection

We may collect device-specific information, it is included your hard drive serial number and machine name, hardware, hardware model, operating system version, unique device identifiers.

When you use our services or view content provided by Flyingbird, we may automatically collect and store certain information in server logs, to make sure the software can be run smoothly. However, we will grantee the security of the information.

Certain services include a unique application number. This number and information about your installation (for example, the operating system type and application version number) may be sent to Flyingbird when you install or uninstall that service or when that service periodically contacts our servers.

We use various technologies to collect and store information when you visit a Flyingbird service, and this may include sending one or more cookies or anonymous identifiers to your device. We also use cookies and anonymous identifiers when you interact with services we offer to our partners, such as advertising services or Flyingbird features that may appear on other sites.

By choosing to enter and submit the requested information when prompted, you are consenting to Flyingbird's collection, use, and disclosure of such information for the purposes of providing the services to you as outlined herein.

"Search App by Vi-View" is a extension of Chrome, it is used to set mystart.vi-view.com as your homepage of Chrome if you check the box on Primary Notice.If you consent to homepage setting, we may collect your search terms and share with our partners.

### How We Use Your Information

Any information collected will be used only by Flyingbird to improve our products, services and websites. Flyingbird uses information and/or e-mail addresses for internal purposes only and does not sell, lease or rent information to third parties.

Flyingbird may hire certain outside contractors to perform services or functions on our behalf (such as customer support, packaging & shipping). We will only provide those companies the personal information they need to complete the desired service. They are not permitted to use customer information for any other purpose and are obligated to keep your customer information confidential. Information submitted to Flyingbird may be transferred across national boundaries to or from our staff in other countries. Flyingbird will only disclose customer information if required to do so by law, legal process or if in good faith it is deemed necessary for the public interest.

We follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the personally identifiable information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however. Therefore, while we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security. 

### Uninstall Instructions

**Uninstall Vi-view from Windows**  
1.Click Start, and then click Control Panel.  
2\. Under Programs, click Uninstall a Program.  
3\. Double-click Vi-view.  
4\. Click Uninstall.  
5\. Click Close.  
 **Homepage : To reset your homepage in Chrome, please follow these steps**  
1\. Go into Tools>Settings (the tools is the buttons on the top right side with three parallel lines).  
2\. Under the 'On Startup' Click on 'Set Pages'.  
3\. Mouse over the vi-view.com and click button, or type a new link to open at the browser startup.  
4\. Click OK when finish.  
 **Uninstall Search App by Vi-View from Google Chrome**  
1\. Go to chrome://extensions on your chrome URL bar to open your chrome extensions page.  
2\. Click "Disable"or "Delete" options, to disable it or remove from Chrome.

### Privacy Issues and Concerns & Altering or Correcting Information

At any time you may review, alter or remove any personal information, including the permitted uses of your personal information, by contacting Vi-view at:  
Company Name: Flyingbird Technology Limited  
Address: FLAT/RM 110，KING‘S COMMERCIAL BUILDING，2-4 CHATHAM COURT，TSIM SHA TSUI，KL，Hong Kong  
Email: [admin@vi-view.com](mailto:admin@vi-view.com)
